<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PCODMaster</string>
    <string name="ecg">ECG</string>
    <string name="temp">Temp</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="heart_rate">Heart Rate:</string>
    <string name="tempreature">Tempreature:</string>
    <string name="ambient_temp">Ambient Temp:</string>
    <string name="the_r_union_swamphen_porphyrio_caerulescens_also_known_as_the_r_union_gallinule_or_oiseau_bleu_french_for_quot_blue_bird_quot_is_a_hypothetical_extinct_species_of_rail_that_was_endemic_to_the_mascarene_island_of_r_union_while_only_known_from_17th_and_18th_century_accounts_by_visitors_to_the_island_it_was_scientifically_named_in_1848_based_on_the_1674_account_by_sieur_dubois_a_considerable_literature_was_subsequently_devoted_to_its_possible_affinities_with_current_researchers_agreeing_it_was_derived_from_the_swamphen_genus_porphyrio_it_has_been_considered_mysterious_and_enigmatic_due_to_the_lack_of_any_physical_evidence_of_its_existence_this_bird_was_described_as_entirely_blue_in_plumage_with_a_red_beak_and_legs_it_was_said_to_be_the_size_of_a_r_union_ibis_or_chicken_which_could_mean_65_70_cm_26_28_in_in_length_and_it_may_have_been_similar_to_the_takahe_while_easily_hunted_it_was_a_fast_runner_and_able_to_fly_though_it_did_so_reluctantly_it_may_have_fed_on_plant_matter_and_invertebrates_as_do_other_swamphens_and_was_said_to_nest_among_grasses_and_aquatic_ferns_it_was_only_found_on_the_plaine_des_cafres_plateau_to_which_it_may_have_retreated_during_the_latter_part_of_its_existence_whereas_other_swamphens_inhabit_lowland_swamps_while_the_last_unequivocal_account_is_from_1730_it_may_have_survived_until_1763_but_overhunting_and_the_introduction_of_cats_probably_drove_it_to_extinction">The Réunion swamphen (Porphyrio caerulescens), also known as the Réunion gallinule or oiseau bleu (French for \"blue bird\"), is a hypothetical extinct species of rail that was endemic to the Mascarene island of Réunion. While only known from 17th- and 18th-century accounts by visitors to the island, it was scientifically named in 1848, based on the 1674 account by Sieur Dubois. A considerable literature was subsequently devoted to its possible affinities, with current researchers agreeing it was derived from the swamphen genus Porphyrio. It has been considered mysterious and enigmatic due to the lack of any physical evidence of its existence. This bird was described as entirely blue in plumage with a red beak and legs. It was said to be the size of a Réunion ibis or chicken, which could mean 65–70 cm (26–28 in) in length, and it may have been similar to the takahe. While easily hunted, it was a fast runner and able to fly, though it did so reluctantly. It may have fed on plant matter and invertebrates, as do other swamphens, and was said to nest among grasses and aquatic ferns. It was only found on the Plaine des Cafres plateau, to which it may have retreated during the latter part of its existence, whereas other swamphens inhabit lowland swamps. While the last unequivocal account is from 1730, it may have survived until 1763, but overhunting and the introduction of cats probably drove it to extinction.</string>
</resources>